http://www.browsermedia.co.uk/privacy-statement/

× Who?What?Why?ClientsBlogJobsContact+44 (0)207 099 0945+ 1 (888) 927-4854 Skip to contentBrowser Media is committed to protecting your privacy.By using this website, you are not sharing any personal information. The website does use cookies (see below) but no personal data is captured unless you choose to fill out one of the following contact forms:Enquiry form (please click on the envelope icon above)Chat window (please click on the chat icon, if available)Newsletter sign upQuestionnaireThese forms do include personal information but we will only use it to deal with your enquiry / add you to the newsletter distribution list / understand your marketing objectives. We will never pass any data to a 3rd party organisation, other than Mailchimp which we use for the newsletter distribution or Chatra, which we use for the chat feature. Mailchimp is GDPR compliant and you have the ability to unsubscribe from Browser Media Bytes at any point and delete any personal data.We are required to be open about our use of personal data and you are entitled to enquire about the data that we hold about you. We welcome any such enquiries and will delete any data at your request.Cookie PolicyOur website uses cookies, as almost all websites do, to help provide you with the best experience we can. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer or mobile phone when you browse websites. On your first visit to this site, you should see a prompt asking you if you are happy to accept the use of cookies. By agreeing to this, it is assumed that you are happy to continue using this website.Our cookies help us:Make our website work as you’d expectRemember your settings during and between visitsImprove the speed/security of the siteAllow users to engage with the blog by adding comments. We use Disqus to manage all comments on the blog. You can read their privacy policy here.We do not use cookies to:Collect any personally identifiable information (without your express permission)Collect any sensitive information (without your express permission)Pass personally identifiable data to third partiesAnonymous Visitor Statistics CookiesWe use Google Analytics as a web analytics solution. Google Analytics uses cookies to compile data on how visitors use this site, the technology they are using and where they came from. This helps us to continuously improve our website. The data is anonymous and not linked to any personal data about you. You can read more about Google Analytics data practices here.Remarketing CookiesWe use Google Ads to show ads to users of this website on other websites. This is known as remarking and requires the use of cookies.  We are unable to proactively reach out to you using any personal data as the whole process is entirely anonymised. By turning off cookies, you will be excluded from seeing any remarking banners. You are also able to control your ad settings within your Google account.Turning Cookies OffYou can usually switch cookies off by adjusting your browser settings to stop it from accepting cookies (please see https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416 for guidance on how to do this). Doing so however will likely limit the functionality of our’s and a large proportion of the world’s websites as cookies are a standard part of most modern websites.Browser Media welcomes any questions should you have any concerns at all – we treat your privacy very seriously. Search for:
First name:*Surname:*I would like you to:*Call meEmail meYour Email:* Your Phone No.:*How can we help you?:*Privacy*
I give consent for Browser Media to process my data in order to deal with my enquiry.NameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged. Send Enquiry
Like most websites, we use cookies to ensure that we give you the best user experience. By continuing to browse the site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies.OkRead more
